The sky is turning violet and gold
The greatest story that we ever told
We're chasing down the edge of the light
Before the city gears into the night
Out on the horizon line
Where the earth and the heavens align
We are running out of time
The
analog is fading away We're leaving behind the
static of the day The engine
hums a frequency clear
The final destination is near
Out on the horizon line
Earth and the heavens align We are running out of
time
Horizon
line The colors bleed, the shadows fall We're
standing at the edge of it all We hold the knife,
we hold the breath There is nothing left
Out on
the
horizon line
We
are
running out of time Out
on the horizon line The
horizon line
The fading light